A Guide to the Papers of William Belser Spong, 1957-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES VII: MICROFILMS, COMPUTER DATA TAPES & REEL TO REEL TAPE RECORDINGS, 16 mm microfilms (Box 67-70)
  - AUDIO TAPE RECORDINGS
    - "Primary Roundup News: Tape #2" n.d. (Reel T-895)
    - "General Election Roundup News" n.d. (Reel T-896)
    - "The Constitution and Foreign Policy," a speech at the College of William & Mary 1974 FEB 15, Cassette (Reel T-897)
- SERIES VIII: NOTEBOOKS
  - Senate Roll Call Votes 1967-1972, 9 volumes